{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "A Temperature Control system is known as:",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Process Control System",
        "b": "Servomechanism",
        "c": "Cascade Control System",
        "d": "None of These"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The time constant of a servo control system can be decreased by",
      "answers": {
        "a": " decreasing the inertia of the system",
        "b": "decreasing the damping of the system",
        "c": "All of the above",
        "d": "None of these"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the transducer not used for the measurement of temperature.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Thermocouple",
        "b": "RVDT",
        "c": "RTD",
        "d": "Pyrometer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "RTD and Thermistors are _____ transducers.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Passive and Analog",
        "b": "Passive and digital",
        "c": "Active and digital",
        "d": "Active and Analog"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The function of the proportional mode is to ____________?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Provide Gain",
        "b": "Eliminate Offsets",
        "c": "To speed up the response and minimize the overshoot",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	{
      "question": "The function of the proportional plus integral mode is to ____________?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Provide Gain",
        "b": "Eliminate Offsets",
        "c": "To speed up the response and minimize the overshoot",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },	
	
	{
      "question": "Gain and proportional bands are",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Two different control modes",
        "b": "Reciprocally related",
        "c": "Adjusted independently 0f one another",
        "d": "Controller functions calibrated in time units"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
      "question": "Physical parameters change due to ______",
      "answers": {
        "a": "voltage",
        "b": "internal and external disturbances",
        "c": "Current",
        "d": "Power"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	
	{
      "question": "What is a process control system?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "system to keep the parameters at zero value",
        "b": " system to maintain the parameters constant",
        "c": "system to keep the parameters at highest value",
        "d": "system to check the voltage"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
      "question": "What is the main objective of process control?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "to control mechanical parameters",
        "b": "to control physical parameters",
        "c": "to control optical parameters",
        "d": " to control electrical parameters"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
	
  ]
}

